Espy, Watt; Papers apap301
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Writings by Others, 1965-2002; Undated; 7; 2.5 cubic ft.; 2.5 cu. ft.
  - Lawes, Lewis, 1969 (Box 67 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 32)
  - Lewis, Dorothy, Jonathan Picus, Marilyn Feldmen, Lori Jackson and Barbara Bard, 1986 (Box 67 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 33)
  - Liebman, Ellen, 1985 (Box 67 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 34)
  - Lilly, Robert, 1996 (Box 67 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 35)
  - Lincoln, James, 1987 (Box 67 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 36)
  - Little, Joseph, 1983-1984 (Box 67 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 37)
  - Mackey, David, 1984 (Box 67 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 38)
  - McFarland, Sam, 1983 (Box 67 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 39)
  - Mitchell, William, 1990 (Box 67 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 40)
  - Protess, David, 1995 (Box 67 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 41)
  - Raalte, Ronald, 1983 (Box 67 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 42)
  - Radelet, Michael, 1981; 1983; 1985-1987; 1989; Undated (Box 67 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 43)
  - Radin, Margaret, 1980 (Box 67 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 44)
  - Sherman, Lawrence and Robert Langworthy, 1979 (Box 67 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 45)
  - Smykla, John, 1986; Undated (Box 67 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 46)
  - Strafer, Richard, 1983 (Box 67 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 47)
  - Streib, Victor, 1982-1983 (Box 67 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 48)
  - Streib, Victor, 1984-1986 (Box 67 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 49)
  - Streib, Victor, 1986-1987 (Box 67 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 50)
  - Streib, Victor, 1987-1988 (Box 68 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 1)
  - Streib, Victor, 1988-1989 (Box 68 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 2)
  - Streib, Victor, 1989-1990 (Box 68 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 3)
  - Streib, Victor, 1991-1992 (Box 68 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 4)
  - Streib, Victor, 1993-1995 (Box 68 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 5)
  - Streib, Victor, 1996-1998; Undated (Box 68 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 6)
  - Streib, Victor and Lynn Sametz, 1982; 1989 (Box 68 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 7)
  - Stutzman, Tod, Undated (Box 68 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 8)
  - Tabak, Ronald, 1995-1996; 1998; 2002 (Box 69 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 1)
  - Texada, David, 1968 (Box 69 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 2)
  - Tolnay, Stewart, E.M. Beck and James Massey, 1989; 1992 (Box 69 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 3)
  - Vrofsky, Melvin, 1984 (Box 69 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 4)
  - Vandiver, Margaret, 1983 (Box 69 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 5-6)
  - Vandiver, Margaret, 1984-1986 (Box 69 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 7)
  - Vandiver and Radelet notes, Florida executions and clemency, Undated (Oversized 10)
  - Ware, Leland, 1989 (Box 69 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 8)
  - Wasserman, Ira, 1980; Undated (Box 69 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 9)
  - White, Welsh, 1983 (Box 69 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 10)
  - Winick, Bruce, 1982 (Box 69 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 11)
  - Zehr, Howard, Undated (Box 69 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 12)
  - Zimring, Franklyn, Undated (Box 69 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 13)
- Advocacy, 1977-2007; Undated; 8; 4.5 cubic ft.; 4.5 cu. ft.
  Watt Espy amassed materials related to a variety of organizations advocating against capital punishment, for better prison conditions, for human rights, and for an improved and unbiased criminal justice system. The groups vary and may be secular or religious, national, statewide or local. Materials in this series include newsletters, execution alerts, appeals, meeting minutes, and brochures. In some instances, it is possible to determine that Espy was active within or supported a particular organization as his name appears in meeting minutes or related papers.
  - Alabama Capital Representation Resource Center Alabama Capital Reporter, 1989-1995 (Box 70 (8-Advocacy), Folder 1-2)
  - Alabama Coalition Against the Death Penalty (ACADP), 1983-1986; 1991-1993 (Box 70 (8-Advocacy), Folder 3)
  - Alabama Committee to Abolish the Death Penalty (ACADP), 1994-1996 (Box 70 (8-Advocacy), Folder 4)
  - Alabama Committee to Abolish the Death Penalty (ACADP), 1996-2002 (Box 70 (8-Advocacy), Folder 5)
  - Alabama Prison Project, 1983-1987; 1989; 1993-1994; 1996-2001; Undated (Box 70 (8-Advocacy), Folder 6)
  - American Civil Liberties Union, Undated (Box 70 (8-Advocacy), Folder 7)
  - American Indians and the Death Penalty, Undated (Box 70 (8-Advocacy), Folder 8)
  - America's Most Wanted, 1991-1992 (Box 70 (8-Advocacy), Folder 9)
  - Amnesty International, 1980-2000; Undated (Box 70 (8-Advocacy), Folder 10)
  - As A Matter of Conscience, 1988 (Box 70 (8-Advocacy), Folder 11)
  - California Appellate Project, RECAP (Sept.-Dec.), 1985 (Box 70 (8-Advocacy), Folder 12)
  - California Appellate Project, RECAP (Jan.-June), 1986 (Box 70 (8-Advocacy), Folder 13)
  - California Appellate Project, RECAP (July-Dec.), 1986 (Box 70 (8-Advocacy), Folder 14)
  - California Appellate Project, RECAP (Jan. - June), 1987 (Box 70 (8-Advocacy), Folder 15)
  - California Appellate Project, RECAP (July-Dec.), 1987 (Box 70 (8-Advocacy), Folder 16)
  - California Appellate Project, RECAP (Jan.-May), 1988 (Box 70 (8-Advocacy), Folder 17)
  - California Appellate Project, RECAP (July-Nov.), 1988 (Box 70 (8-Advocacy), Folder 18)
  - California Appellate Project, RECAP (Feb.-July), 1989 (Box 70 (8-Advocacy), Folder 19)
  - California Appellate Project RECAP (Aug.-Oct.), 1989 (Box 70 (8-Advocacy), Folder 20)
  - California Appellate Project RECAP (Jan.-June), 1990 (Box 71 (8-Advocacy), Folder 1)
  - California Appellate Project RECAP (July-Nov.), 1990 (Box 71 (8-Advocacy), Folder 2)
  - California Appellate Project RECAP (Feb., April, May, June), 1991 (Box 71 (8-Advocacy), Folder 3)
  - California Appellate Project RECAP (Sept., Dec.), 1991 (Box 71 (8-Advocacy), Folder 4)
  - California Appellate Project RECAP (Jan., March, April, July, Oct., Dec.), 1992 (Box 71 (8-Advocacy), Folder 5)
  - California Appellate Project RECAP, 1993 (Box 71 (8-Advocacy), Folder 6)
  - California Appellate Project RECAP, 1994 (Box 71 (8-Advocacy), Folder 7)
  - California Appellate Project RECAP (Jan.-June), 1995 (Box 71 (8-Advocacy), Folder 8)
  - California Appellate Project RECAP (July-Dec.), 1995 (Box 71 (8-Advocacy), Folder 9)
  - California Appellate Project RECAP (Jan-June), 1996 (Box 71 (8-Advocacy), Folder 10)
  - California Appellate Project RECAP (July-Nov.), 1996 (Box 71 (8-Advocacy), Folder 11)
  - California Appellate Project RECAP (Jan-May), 1997 (Box 71 (8-Advocacy), Folder 12)
  - California Appellate Project RECAP (June-Sept.), 1997 (Box 71 (8-Advocacy), Folder 13)
  - California Appellate Project RECAP (Oct-Dec), 1997 (Box 71 (8-Advocacy), Folder 14)
  - California Appellate Project RECAP (Jan-May), 1998 (Box 71 (8-Advocacy), Folder 15)
  - California Appellate Project RECAP (June-Sept), 1998 (Box 71 (8-Advocacy), Folder 16)
  - California Appellate Project RECAP (Oct-Dec), 1998 (Box 71 (8-Advocacy), Folder 17)
  - California Appellate Project RECAP (Jan.-March), 1999 (Box 72 (8-Advocacy), Folder 1)
  - California Appellate Project RECAP (April-June), 1999 (Box 72 (8-Advocacy), Folder 2)
  - California Appellate Project RECAP (July-Dec.), 1999 (Box 72 (8-Advocacy), Folder 3)
  - California Appellate Project RECAP (Jan.-March), 2000 (Box 72 (8-Advocacy), Folder 4)
  - California Appellate Project RECAP (April-June), 2000 (Box 72 (8-Advocacy), Folder 5)
  - California Appellate Project RECAP (July-Sept.), 2000 (Box 72 (8-Advocacy), Folder 6)
  - California Appellate Project RECAP (Oct., Nov.), 2000 (Box 72 (8-Advocacy), Folder 7)
  - California Appellate Project RECAP (Jan.-April), 2001 (Box 72 (8-Advocacy), Folder 8)
  - California Appellate Project RECAP (April-Aug.), 2001 (Box 72 (8-Advocacy), Folder 9)
  - California Appellate Project RECAP (Nov., Dec.), 2001 (Box 72 (8-Advocacy), Folder 10)
  - California Appellate Project RECAP (Jan.-Sept.), 2002 (Box 72 (8-Advocacy), Folder 11)
  - California Appellate Project RECAP (Oct.-Dec.), 2002 (Box 72 (8-Advocacy), Folder 12)
  - Catholics Against Capital Punishment CACP News Notes, 1992-2001; 2005-2007 (Box 72 (8-Advocacy), Folder 13)
  - Citizens and Parliamentarians Campaign for the Abolition of the Death Penalty Worldwide by 2000, 1994 (Box 72 (8-Advocacy), Folder 14)
  - Citizens United for Alternatives to the Death Penalty, 1997-1998 (Box 72 (8-Advocacy), Folder 15)
  - Criminal Justice Newsletter, 1987 (Box 72 (8-Advocacy), Folder 16)
  - Colorado Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty, 1987-1990 (Box 72 (8-Advocacy), Folder 17)
  - CURE - Citizens United for Rehabilitation of Errants, 1987-1997; 1999-2001 (Box 72 (8-Advocacy), Folder 18)
  - Dallas Coalition Against the Death Penalty-The Clarion, 1986-1988 (Box 72 (8-Advocacy), Folder 19)
  - The Death Penalty Exchange, 1987-1989 (Box 72 (8-Advocacy), Folder 20)
  - Death Penalty Information Center, 1999 (Box 72 (8-Advocacy), Folder 21)
  - Death Penalty Update, 1983 (Box 72 (8-Advocacy), Folder 22)
  - The Death Row Forum, 1994 (Box 72 (8-Advocacy), Folder 23)
  - District of Columbia Coalition Against the Death Penalty, 1984 (Box 72 (8-Advocacy), Folder 24)
  - East Bay Justice Project/Death Penalty Focus of California The Sentry, 1984-2007 (Box 72 (8-Advocacy), Folder 25)
  - Endeavor, Live Voices from Death Row, 1989-1993; Undated (Box 72 (8-Advocacy), Folder 26)
  - Equal Justice Initiative of Alabama, Undated (Box 72 (8-Advocacy), Folder 27)
  - Equal Justice Initiative of Alabama EJI Legal Quarterly, 1996-2001 (Box 73 (8-Advocacy), Folder 1)
  - Equal Justice Initiative of Alabama EJI Legal Quarterly, 1996-2001 (Box 73 (8-Advocacy), Folder 2)
  - Fortune Society, Fortune News, 1992-1996 (Box 73 (8-Advocacy), Folder 3)
  - Friends Committee to Abolish the Death Penalty The Quaker Abolitionist, 1996-1997 (Box 73 (8-Advocacy), Folder 4)
  - Friends Outside, 1993 (Box 73 (8-Advocacy), Folder 5)
  - The Fully Informed Jury Association, Undated (Box 73 (8-Advocacy), Folder 6)
  - Georgia Committee Against the Death Penalty, Undated (Box 73 (8-Advocacy), Folder 7)
  - Hospitality, 1998-2001 (Box 73 (8-Advocacy), Folder 8)
  - Illinois Coalition Against the Death Penalty, 1981; 1984-1995 (Box 73 (8-Advocacy), Folder 9-10)
  - Institute for Southern Studies, Undated (Box 73 (8-Advocacy), Folder 11)
  - Institute of Human Relations, 1988 (Box 73 (8-Advocacy), Folder 12)
  - Justice and Mercy Project, 1987; Undated (Box 73 (8-Advocacy), Folder 13)
  - Kentucky Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty, 1990 (Box 73 (8-Advocacy), Folder 14)
  - The Lamp of Hope Project Texas Death Row Journal, 1992; 1994-1995 (Box 73 (8-Advocacy), Folder 15)
  - Law Enforcement Memorial Association (LEMA), 2000 (Box 73 (8-Advocacy), Folder 16)
  - Let Live, 1987-1989; Undated (Box 73 (8-Advocacy), Folder 17)
  - Lockdown, Undated (Box 73 (8-Advocacy), Folder 18)
  - Louisiana Citizens for Life/Pilgrimage for Life, Undated (Box 73 (8-Advocacy), Folder 19)
  - Louisiana Coalition on Jails and Prisons, Louisiana Citizens Against the Death Penalty, 1977-1984; Undated (Box 73 (8-Advocacy), Folder 20)
  - Louisiana Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty/Pilgrimage Peace and Justice Center, 1988-1995 (Box 73 (8-Advocacy), Folder 21)
  - Massachusetts Campaign Against Restoration of the Death Penalty (MCARDP), 1982 (Box 73 (8-Advocacy), Folder 22)
  - Massachusetts Citizens Against the Death Penalty, 1983-1986; 1989-1991 (Box 73 (8-Advocacy), Folder 23)
  - Michigan Coalition Against the Death Penalty, 1981 (Box 73 (8-Advocacy), Folder 24)
  - Missourians to Abolish the Death Penalty, 1999 (Box 73 (8-Advocacy), Folder 25)
  - Murder Victims Families for Reconciliation, 1991; 1999-2000; Undated (Box 73 (8-Advocacy), Folder 26)
  - NAACP Legal Defense and Educational Fund, Death Row U.S.A., 1998-1999 (Box 73 (8-Advocacy), Folder 27)
  - NAACAP Legal Defense and Educational Fund, Death Row U.S.A., 2000 (Box 73 (8-Advocacy), Folder 28)
  - National Alliance Against Racist and Political Repression, 1983; Undated (Box 73 (8-Advocacy), Folder 29)
  - National Coalition Against the Death Penalty, National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty, 1984-1988; 2000 (Box 73 (8-Advocacy), Folder 30)
  - National Coalition Against the Death Penalty, National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty Lifelines, 1981-1985 (Box 73 (8-Advocacy), Folder 31)
  - National Coalition Against the Death Penalty, National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty Lifelines, 1986-1989 (Box 73 (8-Advocacy), Folder 32)
  - National Coalition Against the Death Penalty, National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty Lifelines, 1991-1995 (Box 73 (8-Advocacy), Folder 33)
  - National Coalition Against the Death Penalty, National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty Lifelines, 1997-2001 (Box 73 (8-Advocacy), Folder 34)
  - National Coalition Against the Death Penalty, Execution Alerts, 1984-1993 (Box 73 (8-Advocacy), Folder 35)
  - National Coalition Against the Death Penalty, Execution Alerts, 1995; 1997-2000 (Box 73 (8-Advocacy), Folder 36)
  - National Coalition Against the Death Penalty, Execution Alerts, 2001-2002 (Box 73 (8-Advocacy), Folder 37)
  - National Committee to Reopen the Rosenberg Case, 2000-2001 (Box 73 (8-Advocacy), Folder 38)
  - National Legal Aid and Defender Association Capital Report, 1991 (Box 73 (8-Advocacy), Folder 39)
  - National Practitioners Network for Fathers and Families and the Family Corrections Network, 2000 (Box 73 (8-Advocacy), Folder 40)
  - Nebraskans Against the Death Penalty, 1994-1996; 1998-2001 (Box 73 (8-Advocacy), Folder 41)
  - New York State Defenders Association The Defender, 1985-1986 (Box 74 (8-Advocacy), Folder 1)
  - New York State Defenders Association The Defender, 1987-1989 (Box 74 (8-Advocacy), Folder 2)
  - North Carolinians Against the Death Penalty, 1988 (Box 74 (8-Advocacy), Folder 3)
  - Oregon Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty, 1996-1997 (Box 74 (8-Advocacy), Folder 4)
  - Peacework, 1999 (Box 74 (8-Advocacy), Folder 5)
  - Penny Resistance, 1985 (Box 74 (8-Advocacy), Folder 6)
  - People Abolishing the Death Penalty, 1990 (Box 74 (8-Advocacy), Folder 7)
  - Police Gazette, 1976 (Oversized 1, Folder 5)
  - Police Record Detective, 1948 (Oversized 1, Folder 6)
  - Prison, 1979 (Box 74 (8-Advocacy), Folder 8)
  - Project Hope, A Christian Perspective, 1993-1998; 2000 (Box 74 (8-Advocacy), Folder 9)
  - Project Hope On Wings of Hope, 1993-2002 (Box 74 (8-Advocacy), Folder 10)
  - The Prometheus Foundation Fire!, 1981-1982 (Box 74 (8-Advocacy), Folder 11)
  - Quixote Center and Equal Justice U.S.A., 1987-1990; 2000-2001; Undated (Box 74 (8-Advocacy), Folder 12)
  - South Carolina Coalition Against the Death Penalty, 1984-1985 (Box 74 (8-Advocacy), Folder 13)
  - Southern Coalition on Jails and Prisons, 1984-1990 (Box 75 (8-Advocacy), Folder 1)
  - Southern Poverty Law Center, 1979-1980; 1983 (Box 75 (8-Advocacy), Folder 2)
  - Straight Law, 1991 (Box 75 (8-Advocacy), Folder 3)
  - Tuscaloosa and West Alabama Coalition Against the Death Penalty, 1983-1985; Undated (Box 75 (8-Advocacy), Folder 4)
  - Utah Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty, 1989 (Box 75 (8-Advocacy), Folder 5)
  - The Vision, 1999-2000 (Box 75 (8-Advocacy), Folder 6)
  - Washington Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty, 1992 (Box 75 (8-Advocacy), Folder 7)
  - West Virginians Against the Death Penalty The Abolitionist, 1988-1990 (Box 75 (8-Advocacy), Folder 8)
- Publications, 1929-2001; Undated; 9; 14.4 cubic ft.; 14.4 cu. ft.
  Arranged alphabetically by title, then chronologically within each title.
  For over thirty years, Watt Espy assembled true crime, penitentiary, detective, western U.S. life and culture, and legal publications containing articles about capital crimes, executions, and criminal profiles. The publications date from the 1930s into the 21st Century. While some present straightforward non-fiction explanations of crimes, others feature more sensational accounts with lurid depictions. Of interest are 30 issues of the award-winning The Angolite, a newsmagazine written by prisoners at the Louisiana State Penitentiary. This series also includes more than a half dozen Death Row annuals, featuring profiles and photographs of condemned prisoners, and a set of serial killer, mass murderer and gangster trading cards. Please note that Espy personally bound the publications in boxes 88-90, but did not include all issues for each year in the bound volume. Therefore some publications have both bound and unbound issues.
  - ABA Journal, 1987 January (Box 76 (9-Publications), Folder 1)
  - All True Fact Crime, 1950 October (Box 76 (9-Publications), Folder 2)
  - The Angolite, 1981 (Box 76 (9-Publications), Folder 3)
  - The Angolite, 1984 (Box 76 (9-Publications), Folder 4)
  - The Angolite, 1987 May-1987 August (Box 76 (9-Publications), Folder 5)
  - The Angolite, 1987 September-1987 December (Box 76 (9-Publications), Folder 6)
  - The Angolite, 1988 January-1988 March (Box 76 (9-Publications), Folder 7)
  - The Angolite, 1988 May-1988 August (Box 76 (9-Publications), Folder 8)
  - The Angolite, 1988 September-1988 December (Box 76 (9-Publications), Folder 9)
  - The Angolite, 1989 January-1989 April (Box 77 (9-Publications), Folder 1)
  - The Angolite, 1989 May-1989 August (Box 77 (9-Publications), Folder 2)
  - The Angolite, 1989 September-1989 December (Box 77 (9-Publications), Folder 3)
  - The Angolite, 1990 January-1990 April (Box 77 (9-Publications), Folder 4)
  - The Angolite, 1990 May-1990 August (Box 77 (9-Publications), Folder 5)
  - The Angolite, 1990 September-1990 December (Box 77 (9-Publications), Folder 6)
  - The Angolite, 1990 January-1990 June (Box 77 (9-Publications), Folder 7)
  - The Angolite, 1990 July-1990 October (Box 77 (9-Publications), Folder 8)
  - The Angolite, 1991 November-1999 December (Box 77 (9-Publications), Folder 9)
  - Bad Guys of the Old West, Undated (Box 77 (9-Publications), Folder 10)
  - Baffling Detective Mysteries, 1943 March (Box 77 (9-Publications), Folder 11)
  - Best Detective Cases, 1997 (Box 77 (9-Publications), Folder 12)
  - The Best of the West, 1984-1985 (Box 77 (9-Publications), Folder 13)
  - Best True Fact Detective, 1948; 1951 (Box 77 (9-Publications), Folder 14)
  - Best True Fact Detective, 1955; 1974 (Box 77 (9-Publications), Folder 15)
  - Best West, 1967 August (Box 77 (9-Publications), Folder 16)
  - Chronicle of the Old West, 2001 February (Box 77 (9-Publications), Folder 17)
  - Code 5 Detective, 1972-1973; 1975 (Box 77 (9-Publications), Folder 18)
  - Confidential Detective, 1961 (Box 77 (9-Publications), Folder 19)
  - Confidential Detective, 1964-1965 (Box 77 (9-Publications), Folder 20)
  - Confidential Detective, 1955; 1960 (Box 77 (9-Publications), Folder 21)
  - Corrections Magazine, 1974 (Box 77 (9-Publications), Folder 22)
  - Crime Beat, 1991 (Box 77 (9-Publications), Folder 23)
  - Crime Beat, 1992 January-1992 August (Box 77 (9-Publications), Folder 24)
  - Crime Beat, 1992 November-1993 (Box 77 (9-Publications), Folder 25)
  - Crime Detective, 1957; 1965 (Box 78 (9-Publications), Folder 1)
  - Crime Expose, 1958 January (Box 78 (9-Publications), Folder 2)
  - Crimes of Passion, 1973 (Box 78 (9-Publications), Folder 3)
  - Crime Watch, 1992 (Box 78 (9-Publications), Folder 4)
  - Daring Detective, 1943 February (Box 78 (9-Publications), Folder 5)
  - Deadline Detective, 1972-1973 (Box 78 (9-Publications), Folder 6)
  - Death Row, 1989 (Box 78 (9-Publications), Folder 7)
  - Death Row, 1992 (Box 78 (9-Publications), Folder 8)
  - Death Row, 1993 (Box 78 (9-Publications), Folder 9)
  - Death Row, 1994 (Box 78 (9-Publications), Folder 10)
  - Death Row, 1995 (Box 78 (9-Publications), Folder 11)
  - Death Row, 1996 (Box 78 (9-Publications), Folder 12)
  - Detective Annual, 1951; 1970 (Box 78 (9-Publications), Folder 13)
  - Detective Cases, 1998 February-1999 April (Box 78 (9-Publications), Folder 14)
  - Detective Cases, 1999 June-1999 October (Box 78 (9-Publications), Folder 15)
  - Detective Dragnet, 1997 December-1999 February (Box 78 (9-Publications), Folder 16)
  - Detective Dragnet, 1999 April-1999 October (Box 78 (9-Publications), Folder 17)
  - Detective Files, 1999 January-1999 July (Box 78 (9-Publications), Folder 18)
  - Detective Files, 1997-1998 (Box 78 (9-Publications), Folder 19)
  - Detective Files, 1999 September-2000 May (Box 78 (9-Publications), Folder 20)
  - Detective Files, 2000 July-2001 (Box 78 (9-Publications), Folder 21)
  - Detective World, 1970-1972 (Box 79 (9-Publications), Folder 1)
  - Detective World, 1976; 1978 (Box 79 (9-Publications), Folder 2)
  - Detective Yearbook, 1971-1972 (Box 79 (9-Publications), Folder 3)
  - Espy index to publications- incomplete, Undated (Box 79 (9-Publications), Folder 4)
  - Expose Detective, 1957 (Box 79 (9-Publications), Folder 5)
  - Famous Police Cases, 1952 October (Box 79 (9-Publications), Folder 6)
  - Frontier Times, 1923-1924 (Box 88 (9-Publications), Folder 1)
  - Frontier Times, 1927-1928 (Box 88 (9-Publications), Folder 2)
  - Frontier Times, 1929 (Box 79 (9-Publications), Folder 7)
  - Frontier Times, 1936 (Box 79 (9-Publications), Folder 8)
  - Frontier Times, 1965 (Box 79 (9-Publications), Folder 9)
  - Frontier Times, 1966-1971 (Box 88 (9-Publications), Folder 3-5)
  - Frontier Times, 1971-1973 (Box 79 (9-Publications), Folder 10)
  - Frontier Times, 1972-1973 (Box 88 (9-Publications), Folder 6)
  - Frontier Times, 1974-1979 (Box 89 (9-Publications), Folder 1-3)
  - Frontier Times, 1980-1981 (Box 79 (9-Publications), Folder 11)
  - Frontier Times, 1981; 1984 (Box 79 (9-Publications), Folder 12)
  - Frontier Times, 1985 (Box 79 (9-Publications), Folder 13)
  - Frontier Times Index, Undated (Box 89 (9-Publications), Folder 4)
  - Frontier West, 1974-1975 (Box 79 (9-Publications), Folder 14)
  - Frontier West, 1975-1976 (Box 79 (9-Publications), Folder 15)
  - G Men & Gangster Cards, 1992 (Box 79 (9-Publications), Folder 16)
  - The Gangsters, 1973 (Box 79 (9-Publications), Folder 17)
  - Golden West, 1968; 1970 (Box 79 (9-Publications), Folder 18)
  - Golden West, 1971 (Box 79 (9-Publications), Folder 19)
  - Golden West, 1973-1974 (Box 79 (9-Publications), Folder 20)
  - Great Robberies of the Old West, 1974 June (Box 79 (9-Publications), Folder 21)
  - Great West, 1970-1971; 1974 (Box 79 (9-Publications), Folder 22)
  - Headline Detective, 1952; 1955 (Box 80 (9-Publications), Folder 1)
  - Headquarters Detective, 1941; 1968 (Box 80 (9-Publications), Folder 2)
  - Headquarters Detective, 1970 February; 1997-1998 (Box 80 (9-Publications), Folder 3)
  - Headquarters Detective, 1998 November-1999 September (Box 80 (9-Publications), Folder 4)
  - Headquarters Detective, 2000 March-2001 January (Box 80 (9-Publications), Folder 5)
  - Human Detective, 1945 (Box 80 (9-Publications), Folder 6)
  - Inside the Mafia, Undated (Box 80 (9-Publications), Folder 7)
  - Lady Killers, 1964 (Box 80 (9-Publications), Folder 8)
  - Mafia Trading Cards, 1991 (Box 80 (9-Publications), Folder 9)
  - Master Detective, 1954 November (Box 80 (9-Publications), Folder 10)
  - The National Centurion, 1983 (Box 80 (9-Publications), Folder 11)
  - National Association for Outlaw and Lawman History, 1975-February 1982 (Box 80 (9-Publications), Folder 12)
  - National Association for Outlaw and Lawman History, 1978-1987 (Box 80 (9-Publications), Folder 13)
  - National Detective, 1947-1948 (Box 80 (9-Publications), Folder 14)
  - National Outlaw Lawman Association Newsletter, 1980 December-1981 June (Box 80 (9-Publications), Folder 15)
  - National Outlaw Lawman Association Quarterly, 1980 October; 1981 January; 1981 April (Box 80 (9-Publications), Folder 16)
  - Notes on Publications, Undated (Box 80 (9-Publications), Folder 17)
  - Official Police Detective, 1980 July (Box 80 (9-Publications), Folder 18)